<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ownershipDocument>

    <schemaVersion>X0206</schemaVersion>

    <documentType>3</documentType>

    <periodOfReport>2023-06-29</periodOfReport>

    <noSecuritiesOwned>0</noSecuritiesOwned>

    <issuer>
        <issuerCik>0001830081</issuerCik>
        <issuerName>Rumble Inc.</issuerName>
        <issuerTradingSymbol>RUM</issuerTradingSymbol>
    </issuer>

    <reportingOwner>
        <reportingOwnerId>
            <rptOwnerCik>0001891801</rptOwnerCik>
            <rptOwnerName>Sacks David O</rptOwnerName>
        </reportingOwnerId>
        <reportingOwnerAddress>
            <rptOwnerStreet1>444 GULF OF MEXICO DR</rptOwnerStreet1>
            <rptOwnerStreet2></rptOwnerStreet2>
            <rptOwnerCity>LONGBOAT KEY</rptOwnerCity>
            <rptOwnerState>FL</rptOwnerState>
            <rptOwnerZipCode>34228</rptOwnerZipCode>
            <rptOwnerStateDescription></rptOwnerStateDescription>
        </reportingOwnerAddress>
        <reportingOwnerRelationship>
            <isDirector>1</isDirector>
            <isOfficer>0</isOfficer>
            <isTenPercentOwner>0</isTenPercentOwner>
            <isOther>0</isOther>
            <officerTitle></officerTitle>
            <otherText></otherText>
        </reportingOwnerRelationship>
    </reportingOwner>

    <nonDerivativeTable>
        <nonDerivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Class A Common Stock, par value $0.0001 per share</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>803737</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F1"/>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>I</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
                <natureOfOwnership>
                    <value>See footnote</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F2"/>
                </natureOfOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeHolding>
        <nonDerivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Class A Common Stock, par value $0.0001 per share</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>10224</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F3"/>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>I</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
                <natureOfOwnership>
                    <value>See footnote</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F4"/>
                </natureOfOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeHolding>
        <nonDerivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Class A Common Stock, par value $0.0001 per share</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>246498</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F5"/>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>I</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
                <natureOfOwnership>
                    <value>See footnote</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F6"/>
                </natureOfOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeHolding>
        <nonDerivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Class A Common Stock, par value $0.0001 per share</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>25189</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F7"/>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>I</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
                <natureOfOwnership>
                    <value>See footnote</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F8"/>
                </natureOfOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeHolding>
        <nonDerivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Class A Common Stock, par value $0.0001 per share</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>517576</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F7"/>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>D</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeHolding>
        <nonDerivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Class A Common Stock, par value $0.0001 per share</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>99810</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F7"/>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>I</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
                <natureOfOwnership>
                    <value>See footnote</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F9"/>
                </natureOfOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeHolding>
    </nonDerivativeTable>

    <footnotes>
        <footnote id="F1">Includes 264,853 shares of Class A Common Stock subject to the vesting and forfeiture requirements specified in the Business Combination Agreement, dated as of December 1, 2021, by and between CF Acquisition Corp. VI (n/k/a Rumble Inc.) and Rumble Inc. (n/k/a Rumble Canada Inc.) (the &quot;Business Combination Agreement&quot;).</footnote>
        <footnote id="F2">Represents shares held directly by Craft Ventures II, LP (&quot;Craft Ventures II&quot;). Craft Ventures GP II, LP (&quot;Craft GP II&quot;) is the general partner of Craft GP II, and Mr. Sacks is a managing member of Craft GP II. Mr. Sacks disclaims beneficial ownership of these securities for purposes of Section 16 of the Exchange Act except to the extent of his pecuniary interest therein, if any, and this report shall not be deemed an admission that he is a beneficial owner of such securities for the purpose of Section 16 of the Exchange Act, or for any other purpose.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F3">Includes 3,369 shares of Class A Common Stock subject to the vesting and forfeiture requirements specified in the Business Combination Agreement.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F4">Represents shares held directly by Craft Ventures Affiliates II, LP (&quot;Craft Affiliates&quot;). Craft GP II is the general partner of Craft Affiliates. Mr. Sacks disclaims beneficial ownership of these securities for purposes of Section 16 of the Exchange Act except to the extent of his pecuniary interest therein, if any, and this report shall not be deemed an admission that he is a beneficial owner of such securities for the purpose of Section 16 of the Exchange Act, or for any other purpose.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F5">Includes 86,434 shares of Class A Common Stock that are issuable upon achievement of specified milestones pursuant to that certain Agreement and Plan of Merger, dated May 15, 2023, by and among Rumble, Inc., CallIn Corp. and certain other parties (the &quot;CallIn Merger Agreement&quot;)</footnote>
        <footnote id="F6">Represents shares held directly by Craft Ventures III, LP (&quot;Craft Ventures III&quot;). Craft Ventures GP III, LP (&quot;Craft GP III&quot;) is the general partner of Craft Ventures III and Mr. Sacks is a managing member of Craft GP III. Mr. Sacks disclaims beneficial ownership of these securities for purposes of Section 16 of the Exchange Act except to the extent of his pecuniary interest therein, if any, and this report shall not be deemed an admission that he is a beneficial owner of such securities for the purpose of Section 16 of the Exchange Act, or for any other purpose.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F7">All such shares of Class A Common Stock are issuable upon achievement of specified milestones pursuant to the CallIn Merger Agreement.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F8">Represents shares held directly by Craft Ventures Partners III, LLC (&quot;Craft Partners III&quot;). Mr. Sacks is the sole member of Craft Partners III. Mr. Sacks disclaims beneficial ownership of these securities for purposes of Section 16 of the Exchange Act except to the extent of his pecuniary interest therein, if any, and this report shall not be deemed an admission that he is a beneficial owner of such securities for the purpose of Section 16 of the Exchange Act, or for any other purpose.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F9">Includes 33,270 shares of Class A Common Stock held by each of the Sacks Family 2021 Irrevocable Trust fbo Leighton Natalee Sacks, the Sacks Family 2021 Irrevocable Trust fbo Reagan Nicolette Sacks and Sacks Family 2021 Irrevocable Trust fbo Xavier Xander Sacks. Mr. Sacks disclaims beneficial ownership of these securities for purposes of Section 16 of the Exchange Act except to the extent of his pecuniary interest therein, if any, and this report shall not be deemed an admission that he is a beneficial owner of such securities for the purpose of Section 16 of the Exchange Act, or for any other purpose.</footnote>
    </footnotes>

    <remarks>Exhibit 24 - Power of Attorney</remarks>

    <ownerSignature>
        <signatureName>/s/ Sergey Milyukov, as Attorney-in-Fact</signatureName>
        <signatureDate>2023-07-10</signatureDate>
    </ownerSignature>
</ownershipDocument>