<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ownershipDocument>

    <schemaVersion>X0206</schemaVersion>

    <documentType>3</documentType>

    <periodOfReport>2017-10-18</periodOfReport>

    <noSecuritiesOwned>0</noSecuritiesOwned>

    <issuer>
        <issuerCik>0001441816</issuerCik>
        <issuerName>MongoDB, Inc.</issuerName>
        <issuerTradingSymbol>MDB</issuerTradingSymbol>
    </issuer>

    <reportingOwner>
        <reportingOwnerId>
            <rptOwnerCik>0001222287</rptOwnerCik>
            <rptOwnerName>BOTHA ROELOF</rptOwnerName>
        </reportingOwnerId>
        <reportingOwnerAddress>
            <rptOwnerStreet1>2800 SAND HILL ROAD, SUITE 101</rptOwnerStreet1>
            <rptOwnerStreet2></rptOwnerStreet2>
            <rptOwnerCity>MENLO PARK</rptOwnerCity>
            <rptOwnerState>CA</rptOwnerState>
            <rptOwnerZipCode>94025</rptOwnerZipCode>
            <rptOwnerStateDescription></rptOwnerStateDescription>
        </reportingOwnerAddress>
        <reportingOwnerRelationship>
            <isDirector>1</isDirector>
            <isOfficer>0</isOfficer>
            <isTenPercentOwner>1</isTenPercentOwner>
            <isOther>0</isOther>
        </reportingOwnerRelationship>
    </reportingOwner>

    <derivativeTable>
        <derivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Series C Redeemable Convertible Preferred Stock</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <conversionOrExercisePrice>
                <footnoteId id="F1"/>
            </conversionOrExercisePrice>
            <exerciseDate>
                <footnoteId id="F1"/>
            </exerciseDate>
            <expirationDate>
                <footnoteId id="F1"/>
            </expirationDate>
            <underlyingSecurity>
                <underlyingSecurityTitle>
                    <value>Class B Common Stock</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F2"/>
                </underlyingSecurityTitle>
                <underlyingSecurityShares>
                    <value>3126235</value>
                </underlyingSecurityShares>
            </underlyingSecurity>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>I</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
                <natureOfOwnership>
                    <value>See Footnote</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F3"/>
                </natureOfOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </derivativeHolding>
        <derivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Series D Redeemable Convertible Preferred Stock</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <conversionOrExercisePrice>
                <footnoteId id="F4"/>
            </conversionOrExercisePrice>
            <exerciseDate>
                <footnoteId id="F4"/>
            </exerciseDate>
            <expirationDate>
                <footnoteId id="F4"/>
            </expirationDate>
            <underlyingSecurity>
                <underlyingSecurityTitle>
                    <value>Class B Common Stock</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F2"/>
                </underlyingSecurityTitle>
                <underlyingSecurityShares>
                    <value>2823608</value>
                </underlyingSecurityShares>
            </underlyingSecurity>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>I</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
                <natureOfOwnership>
                    <value>See Footnotes</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F3"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F5"/>
                </natureOfOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </derivativeHolding>
        <derivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Series E Redeemable Convertible Preferred Stock</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <conversionOrExercisePrice>
                <footnoteId id="F6"/>
            </conversionOrExercisePrice>
            <exerciseDate>
                <footnoteId id="F6"/>
            </exerciseDate>
            <expirationDate>
                <footnoteId id="F6"/>
            </expirationDate>
            <underlyingSecurity>
                <underlyingSecurityTitle>
                    <value>Class B Common Stock</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F2"/>
                </underlyingSecurityTitle>
                <underlyingSecurityShares>
                    <value>658011</value>
                </underlyingSecurityShares>
            </underlyingSecurity>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>I</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
                <natureOfOwnership>
                    <value>See Footnote</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F5"/>
                </natureOfOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </derivativeHolding>
        <derivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Series F Redeemable Convertible Preferred Stock</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <conversionOrExercisePrice>
                <footnoteId id="F7"/>
            </conversionOrExercisePrice>
            <exerciseDate>
                <footnoteId id="F7"/>
            </exerciseDate>
            <expirationDate>
                <footnoteId id="F7"/>
            </expirationDate>
            <underlyingSecurity>
                <underlyingSecurityTitle>
                    <value>Class B Common Stock</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F2"/>
                </underlyingSecurityTitle>
                <underlyingSecurityShares>
                    <value>298968</value>
                </underlyingSecurityShares>
            </underlyingSecurity>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>I</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
                <natureOfOwnership>
                    <value>See Footnote</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F5"/>
                </natureOfOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </derivativeHolding>
    </derivativeTable>

    <footnotes>
        <footnote id="F1">The Series C Redeemable Convertible Preferred Stock is convertible into Class B Common Stock on a 1:0.75 basis and has no expiration date.  Immediately prior to the completion of the Issuer's initial public offering, all shares of Series C Redeemable Convertible Preferred Stock will be converted into shares of Class B Common Stock.  As of the date hereof, Sequoia Capital U.S. Venture 2010 Fund, LP holds 3,681,872 shares of Series C Redeemable Convertible Preferred Stock, Sequoia Capital U.S. Venture 2010 Partners Fund (Q), LP holds 404,743 shares of Series C Redeemable Convertible Preferred Stock and Sequoia Capital U.S. Venture 2010 Partners Fund, LP holds 81,699 shares of Series C Redeemable Convertible Preferred Stock.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F2">Each share of Class B Common Stock is convertible at any time at the option of the Reporting Person into one share of Class A Common Stock and has no expiration date. Upon the closing of the Issuer's sale of its Class A Common Stock in its firm commitment underwritten initial public offering pursuant to a registration statement on Form S-1 (File No. 333-220557) under the Securities Act of 1933, as amended, the Class B Common Stock will convert automatically into Class A Common Stock on the same basis upon the earlier of: (i) any transfer, whether or not for value, except for certain &quot;Permitted Transfers&quot; as defined in the Issuer's restated certificate of incorporation in effect as of the date hereof, or (ii) at such time as the outstanding shares of Class B common stock represent less than 10% of the aggregate voting power of the Issuer's capital stock.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F3">The Reporting Person is a director of SC US (TTGP), Ltd.  SC US (TTGP), Ltd. is the general partner of SC U.S. Venture 2010 Management, L.P., which is the general partner of each of Sequoia Capital U.S. Venture 2010 Fund, LP, Sequoia Capital U.S. Venture 2010 Partners Fund (Q), LP and Sequoia Capital U.S. Venture 2010 Partners Fund ,LP, or collectively, the SC 2010 Funds.  The Reporting Person disclaims beneficial ownership of the securities held by the SC 2010 Funds except to the extent of his pecuniary interest therein, and the inclusion of these securities in this report shall not be deemed an admission of beneficial ownership of the reported securities for purposes of Section 16 or for any other purposes.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F4">The Series D Redeemable Convertible Preferred Stock is convertible into Class B Common Stock on a 1:0.75 basis and has no expiration date.  Immediately prior to the completion of the Issuer's initial public offering, all shares of Series D Redeemable Convertible Preferred Stock will be converted into shares of Class B Common Stock.  As of the date hereof, Sequoia Capital U.S. Growth Fund IV, LP holds 3,294,250 shares of Series D Redeemable Convertible Preferred Stock, Sequoia Capital USGF Principals Fund IV, L.P. holds 145,142 shares of Series D Redeemable Convertible Preferred Stock, Sequoia Capital U.S. Venture 2010 Fund, LP holds 287,575 shares of Series D Redeemable Convertible Preferred Stock, Sequoia Capital U.S. Venture 2010 Partners Fund (Q), LP holds 31,468 shares of Series D Redeemable Convertible Preferred Stock and Sequoia Capital U.S. Venture 2010 Partners Fund, LP holds 6,378 shares of Series D Redeemable Convertible Preferred Stock.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F5">The Reporting Person is a director of SC US (TTGP), Ltd.  SC US (TTGP), Ltd. is the general partner of SCGF IV Management, L.P., which is the general partner of Sequoia Capital U.S. Growth Fund IV, L.P. and Sequoia Capital USGF Principals Fund IV, L.P., or collectively, the SC GFIV Funds. The Reporting Person disclaims beneficial ownership of the securities held by the SC GFIV Funds except to the extent of his pecuniary interest therein, and the inclusion of these securities in this report shall not be deemed an admission of beneficial ownership of the reported securities for purposes of Section 16 or for any other purposes.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F6">The Series E Redeemable Convertible Preferred Stock is convertible into Class B Common Stock on a 1:0.75 basis and has no expiration date.  Immediately prior to the completion of the Issuer's initial public offering, all shares of Series E Redeemable Convertible Preferred Stock will be converted into shares of Class B Common Stock.  As of the date hereof, Sequoia Capital U.S. Growth Fund IV, LP holds 840,325 shares of Series E Redeemable Convertible Preferred Stock and Sequoia Capital USGF Principals Fund IV, L.P. holds 37,024 shares of Series E Redeemable Convertible Preferred Stock.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F7">The Series F Redeemable Convertible Preferred Stock is convertible into Class B Common Stock on a 1:0.5 basis and has no expiration date.  Immediately prior to the completion of the Issuer's initial public offering, all shares of Series F Redeemable Convertible Preferred Stock will be converted into shares of Class B Common Stock.  As of the date hereof, Sequoia Capital U.S. Growth Fund IV, LP holds 572,704 shares of Series F Redeemable Convertible Preferred Stock and Sequoia Capital USGF Principals Fund IV, L.P. holds 25,233 shares of Series F Redeemable Convertible Preferred Stock.</footnote>
    </footnotes>

    <remarks>Exhibit 24.1 - Power of Attorney</remarks>

    <ownerSignature>
        <signatureName>/s/ Jung Yeon Son, by power of attorney for Roelof F. Botha</signatureName>
        <signatureDate>2017-10-18</signatureDate>
    </ownerSignature>
</ownershipDocument>